Jiaojiao,
Fu Xiang and his son
are dead.
Uncle,
how did they die?
It's said
they hanged themselves at home.
Probably they did
too many bad things
and were afraid of having too many enemies,
so they ended their lives first.
The Fu family
is like
a deep abyss.
One wrong step
and it's over.
Who is Cheng Qi?
Please come with us.
Sir,
Cheng Qi has already completed the ceremony.
The Ministry of Rites has witnessed it.
The speech contest can now begin.
That's good.
Cheng Qi,
I heard that in the final test of the Star Conference,
your speech is related to Langyue.
Have you been there before?
Your Majesty,
I have never been to Langyue.
My wife is a bodyguard.
Her mother went to Langyue to escort goods when she was alive.
In recent days,
my wife and I have also escorted goods to Klara City.
and saw a little of it.
If so,
if the Yun State and the Langyue State trade,
your wife's escort agency
will be
prosperous.
If we get the support of the royal family,
it should be so.
But the business that is prosperous
is the business of many merchants of the two countries.
Then the speech contest
be based on this theme.
What do you think?
Your Majesty is wise.
When Princess Langyue came this time,
there were many merchants from Langyue.
If this is the theme of the speech,
it will definitely give them more confidence in trade.
Grand Preceptor,
what do you think?
What's wrong with you?
You've been gloomy since you came back.
The topic set by the emperor
shouldn't be difficult for you.
That's not what I'm worried about.
I think
the court is stable,
and the country is prosperous.
It's a great opportunity
to trade with Langyue.
It's also what the people want.
Choosing this topic
and hosting a speech meeting
to invite the Langyue Mission
is just perfect.
However...
Go ahead.
This matter of customs clearance
is ultimately about the livelihood of the people.
The speech contest should reflect
the determination to share joy with the people.
So I suggest
holding it at the palace.
That's not a good idea.
Your Majesty,
this concerns your safety
and that of Princess Langyue.
The palace guards are more reliable.
What if someone breaks in?
The people of the capital live in peace
and prosperity, and you are beloved.
Who would dare to break in?
You...
Your Majesty,
Cheng Qi won the stargazing contest.
And the one in charge of the oratorical contest
is the Su's Escort Agency.
I suggest
the Su's Escort Agency to cooperate with the Ministry of Rites.
I will arrange the guards.
This will ensure the safety of the people of the two countries,
and show the kindness of the emperor,
and the style of Yun State.
Cheng Qi,
what do you think?
I dare not comment.
It's up to you.
Then let's not discuss it further.
As the Grand Preceptor said,
let's make this recitation meeting
a celebration for the people.
Cheng Qi will be in charge of the recitation,
Su's Escort Agency assists the Ministry of Rites.
The Grand Preceptor will coordinate everything.
Make sure the recitation meeting
is held as scheduled.
Yes.
I'll take care of it.
It's all my fault.
I couldn't think of a perfect plan
when things were tense,
which led you
and everyone else
into such danger.
This was a great opportunity.
The royals picked you for the speech.
If the agency holds the poetry competition,
you'll be the royal poet,
and the agency will be the royal agency.
We're not thinking of the same thing.
I don't want to enter the court,
not just because of my father.
Father,
didn't you say you'd make a move at the poetry competition?
Why let Su's Agency hold it?
How do we get in?
And,
the Ministry of War's forces
are all outside of the capital.
It's hard to mobilize them
in time.
From what I've read,
when it comes to court affairs,
one wrong move
can be disastrous.
Don't be so anxious.
If we don't do this,
how can we avoid suspicion?
If the heavens thwart our wishes,
we must defy the heavens.
We should consider carefully
which of our blades
is now faster than the Ministry of War.
The death of Fu Xiang and his son
is definitely not that simple.
And I now suspect that the matter concerning Langyue
is greatly related to the Grand Preceptor.
You mean...
Yikeba?
He wants to stir up the mess
in the Yun State more than we do.
Otherwise, he'll never have a chance to rise.
As for the speech meeting,
I've arranged for your sister
to go with the Su's Escort Agency.
He recommended you to organize
the speech meeting today.
So I'm worried
he wants to use you and me as his pawns.
He's our target.
As for Zhang Xi Yun,
she's been hiding in the courtyard all day.
I think she's just pretending to be sick,
trying to protect herself.
It's not that easy.
By the way,
how's it going with the Ministry of Rites?
Ling Feng is under my control.
His father listens to us.
Then hurry up and find a way
to make Yikeba
our sword.
Okay.
My husband, you are wrong.
The escort's life
is a life of danger.
Yiguana is the princess.
I also do business with her.
My mother said
the escort must be with the goods.
We have a clear conscience.
As long as we are upright
and don't betray the Yun State,
who can treat us as pawns?
I just want you to be safe.
I don't want you to be in danger, you know?
This is our chance to achieve our ambitions together.
Don't you
want to try with me?
Since you said that,
let's try.
And
we're going to be the chess players.
By the way, my dear,
Zhang Xi Yun will work with you
to organize this event.
Why is she everywhere?
Did you ask her to come?
It's all arranged by the Grand Preceptor.
Why?
He could have just let Zhang Xi Yun do it.
So I said this matter is not that simple.
I guess
they will make a move at the speech meeting.
We'll see what they do.
Thanks to the official's love,
with the style of the Yun State,
I hereby announce
the Moonlight Speech Meeting
is officially launched today.
The Su's Escort Agency has been escorting for generations,
and we have encountered countless disasters.
We've all survived.
Now,
the best opportunity is right in front of us.
If we succeed in this trade,
we will no longer worry
about the business of the Escort Agency.
From now on,
all the people in the Agency
will be devoted to the meeting.
Everyone must write down what they have to do
and post it on the head of the bed.
Make progress every day
and report at any time.
Brother,
you are in charge of props and scenery.
No problem.
Gong Xi, Fa Cai.
You are in charge of all musicians
and dancers.
Make sure to supervise the rehearsal.
Yes, boss.
Mr. Meng,
I'm very relieved
to handle the performance.
This time, I have a surprise for you.
I'll definitely show the Langyue Mission
the elegance of the Yun State.
The top musician in Yunjing,
do you know what to do?
I can't wait.
Uncle,
you take the escort team to guard the outside.
That means
I can't attend the speech contest, right?
You are the most important person in the Escort Agency.
The most important part can only be entrusted to you.
Although it's flattery,
it feels much better.
The official has already written the theme for the speech meeting.
We must remember it.
There is no distance between mountains and waters.
Clouds and the moon are of one family.
Wait.
Zhang Gongzi.
General, please don't blame me.
The Princess hasn't arrived in Yunjing,
but they're already posting a reward for you.
Let's just bear with it for now.
Once they arrive in Yunjing,
I'll kill that girl.
He and Bai Yanliang are both Moonlight Envoys.
They have heavy guards.
Don't even think about killing her.
It's hard to get close to her now.
And if you kill her now,
you'll never return to the Moonlight Sect.
You'll die if you go back.
So?
What's the point of killing her and Bai Yanli?
You can't stay in the Yunjing.
Unless...
The king of Langyue is changed.
You're
so ambitious.
I can't kill the king of Langyue.
What if the Yun State sends troops to attack Langyue?
Your royal family
advocates trade.
They won't attack Langyue
at this time.
If the royal family was killed
at the speech meeting,
do you think the Yun State would send troops?
Killing the royal family in the Yun State?
You want me to die.
It's all a matter of death.
Why not take a big risk?
Besides,
there's still a chance to survive.
My people have arrived in Yunjing.
I need to go out and meet them.
Brother,
the light gathering tool,
the light column needs to be farther.
This time in the Palace,
not like in Huayue Tower,
we may need several light columns.
No problem.
Give me two days,
and I'll make it better.
I heard that Su's Escort Agency has grown,
and you are picky about accepting escorts.
The notice said that
the team of the Princess will arrive in three days.
The team will indeed arrive in three days,
but I missed you,
so I came early.
It's true that you missed us,
but it's not just that, is it?
How's that?
I told you she would ask directly.
I know her best.
Your Highness, you might as well say it.
The silver sent by Fuyun Escort Agency
was caught by us.
During the confiscation, several account books were found.
It involves the Langyue family,
which is in charge of the casting of silver coins.
By the way,
I saw Yunjing was looking for Yikeba.
What's going on?
The money sent by the Fuyun Escort Agency
was for Yikeba.
Unfortunately, he ran away.
Before we left Langyue,
Princess has sent a letter
to request joint arrest.
I'm afraid the Yunjing government
has been infiltrated by that force
and will protect Yikeba.
So
I need you.
If he's in Yunjing,
I'll mobilize the escorts
to investigate.
Princess.
Don't worry.
Take these people inside.
You two split up and follow them.
Okay.
My lady,
the master and the young master are here.
My lord, my lord.
Father, brother.
You should rest.
Leave us.
Yes, sir.
You've been sick for days.
Are you feeling better?
I'm fine.
Father, do you have any orders?
Yes, there is something
I need you to do.
Father, please.
I know
you have a grudge against the Sus.
But the joint hosting of the poetry meeting
is the Emperor's decree.
We can't keep dragging our feet.
It's the Ministry of Rites' responsibility.
I think
you just don't want to see Cheng Qi.
You can't have him, so you're upset.
I never knew
you are such a person.
Father,
I know the speech contest is of great significance.
I'll go to the Ministry of Rites
and Su's Escort Agency in the next few days.
I won't make any mistakes.
As for the speech contest,
you can plan as usual.
But there is one thing.
You need to add a fireworks show to it.
For such a big occasion,
to add fireworks.
It's gonna cost a lot.
Don't worry about the money.
The Ministry of Rites will cover it.
Later, Qijia will tell you how to do it.
Yes.
I'll follow your arrangements.
Take care of yourself.
My lady,
do you really have to go?
The knife is in my hand.
I can't get rid of it.
If I don't stab him,
I'll stab myself.
Cheng Qi's words are really good.
Take a look at the memorial
from the Ministry of Rites.
Fireworks.
Your Majesty,
fireworks
have not been used for many years.
I'm not sure if it's safe
for such an important occasion.
The fireworks for the Lantern Festival
in recent years have been good.
Fireworks are a specialty of our country.
It's a good chance to show the elegance
of our great country to the Langyue people.
Your Majesty is wise.
Setting off fireworks during the concert
is a mess.
What if it catches fire
and burns the props?
If it really catches fire,
it's okay to burn the props,
but if it burns the nobles,
we will lose our heads.
Don't panic.
We can control the distance
and eliminate all hidden dangers.
It will be a highlight of the recitation meeting.
The Princess likes fireworks.
I think the Emperor
wants to make her happy.
I'll go to the Ministry of Rites earlier
to ask for the materials.
We must be perfect.
Gong Xi.
Tell the Princess
Yikeba should be in the Prime Minister's Mansion.
We'll keep an eye on him.
Yes, My Lord.
The Emperor has approved it.
You are so insightful.
I know him
better than anyone else.
He likes to make a quick success.
He likes
such a grand scene the most.
By the way, father,
Mr. Ling sent a message that
Su Yuejiao has been asking him
for the materials of fireworks these days.
So,
should we give it to her or not?
Of course, we should.
But,
you won't go.
My lady,
are you really going alone?
What's up?
You really want to see her?
What are you thinking about?
I'm worried about you.
She can't do anything to me in the daytime.
I've been hiding for so long.
I just want to see
what she wants to do.
Enjoy yourself.
Don't worry.
That's grape juice.
Why does the Ministry of Rites add fireworks
to the recitation meeting?
Since you come straight to the point,
I'll be frank.
I didn't want to be involved,
but I had no choice.
Whether we like it or not,
now
we are in the same boat.
These are the fireworks used before.
They will be sent directly to the agency.
As for how to use them,
I don't need to teach you, do I?
Cheng Qi,
I don't have much time.
Let's make it short.
Yikeba is going to kill the Emperor.
Since you've got the news,
why not just arrest
the instigator behind it?
I think
you can guess who it is.
It's the Grand Preceptor.
For so many years,
he has been scheming
to cultivate his followers.
The court is complicated.
Yikeba
must have been bewitched by the Grand Preceptor
to fight to the death.
His purpose
is to sabotage the relationship between our two countries,
so that he can
profit from it.
The Emperor wants to catch the big snake,
and so do you.
Then I'll quit.
I don't want my wife
and the Escort Agency to get involved.
Besides,
we can't control
the court affairs.
I disagree.
The Emperor has read your works
and tested your depth
when he summoned you.
You have a heart for the world
and a mind for the universe.
His Majesty
considers you
as the pillar of our empire.
This concerns the destiny of our two nations.
You just need to
prepare for your performance.
Don't worry about anything else.
We mustn't let the Grand Preceptor
suspect anything.
I'll find a way to remove the hidden dangers.
Your family's safety
will also be protected.
Actually,
I envy you.
You have family,
friends,
and a husband.
We are both women who stand on our own.
But in the end,
I only have myself.
I have no one behind me.
Am I familiar to you?
Why tell me this?
Musicians and dancers of Huayue Tower,
storehouses of Zhang's shops,
all are mine.
You can use them freely.
Believe it or not,
I have no interest in Cheng Qi anymore.
The fireworks for the speech meeting
are a larger version of this.
One is fireworks,
and the other is explosives.
You need to distinguish them carefully.
You...
What do you mean?
Remember,
the difference between fireworks and explosives
lies in the ratio of the fuse and powder.
They look the same.
Wait.
I'm a bit confused.
Are you trying to help me
or are you trying to harm me?
If something goes wrong at the recitation meeting,
I'll also be held accountable.
You are the daughter of the Grand Preceptor,
while I'm just a humble escort.
If there's blame to be had, it falls on me.
My father and brother
don't cherish me like your family and friends do.
I gave you the explosives,
and you're the one who brought them in.
If something goes wrong,
we're both implicated.
So,
helping you
is helping myself.
Got it?
Instead of wondering why I did this,
you'd better think of a solution.
Zhang Xi Yun gave them to you?
The most strange thing is here.
She told me
one is fireworks,
the other is explosives,
and taught me how to tell them apart,
and how to distinguish them.
I guess what was delivered to the agency this time
are all explosives.
Fireworks?
We have to figure out a way ourselves.
What?
She wants to blow up the agency,
or the speech meeting?
Mr. Yue asked me to meet him today.
He said the Prime Minister would
harm the Emperor at the meeting.
And
he forced the Ministry of Rites to arrange fireworks.
At that time,
the fireworks will turn into explosives.
Yikeba will assassinate the Emperor
at the meeting.
Then we have to stop it.
Otherwise, we will be negligent.
Mr. Yue said
everything should go as planned.
Just to
lure the big fish out.
Big fish?
The Grand Preceptor?
Zhang Xi Yun probably didn't want to be used by her father,
so she reminded you to change the gunpowder.
The court is too treacherous.
Do you really believe Zhang Xi Yun?
I don't know
Zhang Xiuyun's words,
but I'd rather believe
that she's telling the truth.
This morning,
Qianzhi and I have worked out
the fireworks plan.
My lady,
next,
it's up to you to make a switch.
Father,
I've already arranged the people
on the guest list
of the Yun and Langyue Caravans.
I trust you
to handle this.
I'll personally deliver
the fireworks to the escort agency
to avoid any mistakes.
I'll also accompany the performers
into the palace.
You've already made up?
They are just escorts.
Simple-minded.
You go there and keep an eye on them.
If there is any movement,
pay attention to it
and report it in time.
Yes.
Don't tell Grandpa about these things.
In addition to the original division of labor,
you also need to pay attention to your own safety.
Uncle.
You take your brothers
to mark the seats
of all suspicious people.
We'll pay special attention to them.
Okay, I'll do it.
Gong Xi and Facha.
When Jian finished the fireworks,
you need to carry out the fireworks with him.
Make sure everything is perfect.
Got it.
My Lord, what should I do?
You need to protect Meng Feifei
and the musicians who will participate in the speech.
What about you?
I'll protect him.
The fireworks for the speech
can be placed in these positions.
They can match the content of the speech
and will not be dangerous.
Okay.
My Lady,
next, you should push Zhang Xi Yun and the Ministry of Rites
to arrange the fireworks to be transported to the escort agency.
I'll go to the Ministry of Rites now.
They were all inspected before coming in.
If the gunpowder is damp,
it may affect the display tomorrow.
We are ordered to inspect.
Don't stop us.
Please.
Have you checked the two firecrackers?
Yes, I've checked the composition.
How sure are you, bro?
I've made gunpowder before,
but never fireworks.
I was only 50% sure,
but now, after checking these,
I'm at least 90% sure.
Seal the box.
Yes, sir.
I just checked the fireworks with my men.
All confirmed.
Tomorrow, before the speech,
these fireworks
will be stored in a new place.
This is
the official seating area.
Father and brother
are also around.
How can they be placed like this?
Since the emperor
invited people to the palace,
and the fireworks are arranged by the Ministry of Rites,
it must be flawless.
Don't worry.
Have our people
entered the palace?
Don't worry, father.
It's all arranged.
Tomorrow
is a big day for our escort agency.
We should celebrate it.
Grandpa,
we should wait until tomorrow to drink.
My son-in-law, you don't know.
Whenever all the escorts go on a mission,
when they set out,
they celebrate the auspicious start.
When they come back,
they celebrate the safe return.
This part can't be omitted.
Everyone, except for Jiaojiao,
let's have a drink.
No.
Since I took over the agency,
since my first job.
I won't skip it today.
Come on.
Raise your glasses.
The Su family has always valued trust
and duty.
Tomorrow's speech
is our most important escort.
We must stand together.
The escort is our life.
To protect the escort of the Yun State,
let's drink up.
- Cheers! - Cheers!